jarrattdavis.com 2016-10-30

# Privacy Policy - Jarratt Davis

**This privacy policy sets out how Jarratt Davis uses and protects any information that you may give while using this website (JarrattDavis.com). Jarratt Davis is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, and then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement? JarrattDavis.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from May 4th, 2014.**

### **What we collect?**

We may collect the following information:  
– Name or pen-name  
– contact information including email address  
– Demographic information such as geo-locations, preferences and interests other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

### **What we do with the information we gather?**

Jarratt Davis requires this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: Internal record keeping, and proper visitor feedback. Jarratt Davis may use the information to improve our products and services. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

### **Security**

Jarratt Davis is committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information, we collect online.

### **How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. Forex Peace Army use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyses data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### **Links to other websites**

JarrattDavis.com website contains links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other websites. Therefore, Jarratt Davis cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### **Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information by not filling any forms on JarrattDavis.com website. If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by contacting us using contact us form at the bottom of the site pages with the request to modify or delete your personal information previously submitted to JarrattDavis.com

### **How to unsubscribe from our list?**

If you no longer wish to receive communications from JarrattDavis.com website it’s very easy to stop. Simply scroll down to the bottom of any email and click the “unsubscribe” link. Every email that is sent from JarrattDavis.com mailing list is specially coded with a link that is tied to your email subscription account. If you no longer wish to receive emails from JarrattDavis.com, simply scroll to the bottom of the email and click the unsubscribe link.

### **Details of Personal Information**

Jarratt Davis will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. JarrattDavis.com may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which Jarratt Davis think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please send us a message using contact us form at the bottom of the JarrattDavis.com pages. If you believe that any information JarrattDavis.com is holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
